http://www.paliareroland.com/privacy-policy

skip to main content
About PRRR
Why PRRR
We are a litigation boutique with a broad range of expertise and experience. We are routinely involved in Canada's highest profile cases, whether complex commercial litigation or class actions,
professional discipline or labour disputes. We are trusted to manage the most sensitive legal issues facing businesses of every size, individuals, labour unions, professional regulatory bodies, academic institutions, and public interest organizations. We are devoted to excellence in advocacy in every area of our practice.
Read More ...
Related Pages
Why PRRRRepresentative WorkPRRR NewsEvents/Speaking EngagementsDiversity and InclusionPro BonoDoin' GoodAccolades
Why PRRRRepresentative WorkPRRR NewsEvents/Speaking EngagementsDiversity and InclusionPro BonoDoin' GoodAccolades
Lawyers
Featured Lawyer
Kris Borg-Olivier
Email
p: 416.646.7490
Learn More
Our Lawyers
Kris Borg-Olivier
Overview
BMO Class Action Summary JudgmentOur specialized Class Action group is experienced both in prosecuting and defending class proceedings.
The Class Action group is a team of talented lawyers and support staff, with recognized expertise in prosecuting and defending class actions, who devote a significant portion of their practices to this complicated and specialized form of litigation.
Acting as class counsel on some cases, and as defence counsel on others gives the Class Action group unique strategic insight in an area where most firms typically represent only one side or the other.
Read More ...
Current Class Actions
Bank of Montreal RRSPShoppers Drug MartSouthern China Livestock Inc.PayPalAboriginal Treaty Rights Access (ATRA) Passports
Related Pages
Class Action FAQPast Class Actions
Class Action FAQPast Class Actions
Students
Student Program
First and foremost, we are committed to excellence in advocacy. Although a number of the lawyers at Paliare Roland concentrate their practice in specific areas of litigation, no one is required to do so. The firm's culture is rooted firmly in the belief that a good litigator is able to do virtually any type of case. Consequently, the ability to advocate on behalf of a client -- any client -- is the primary skill we look for in a lawyer.
Read More ...
Related Pages
Student ProgramHow to ApplyOur StudentsWhy Paliare Roland?Professional Development & MentorshipDiversity and Inclusion in the ProfessionOur Recruitment Process
Student ProgramHow to ApplyOur StudentsWhy Paliare Roland?Professional Development & MentorshipDiversity and Inclusion in the ProfessionOur Recruitment Process
CareersContactClient Resources
Find a Lawyer
select
Name
Phone
Alysha Shore
416.646.7437
Andrew Lokan
select
Aboriginal Treaty Rights Access (ATRA) PassportsAppeals and Judicial ReviewBank of Montreal RRSPBankruptcy and Insolvency LitigationClass ActionsConstitutional LitigationCopyright and Trademark DisputesCorporate Commercial LitigationDefamationEmployment LawEnergy LawEstates and TrustsHuman RightsJudicial Inquiries and InquestsLabour LawLibel and SlanderMediation and ArbitrationMunicipal and Planning LawPayPalPension LitigationPrivacy and AccessProduct Liability and Tort ClaimsProfessional Discipline and RegulationPublic and Administrative LawSecurities LitigationShoppers Drug MartSouthern China Livestock Inc.White Collar Crime
Privacy Policy
Named one of the top 10 litigation boutiques in Canada. Again.
Privacy Policy
Paliare Roland is committed to providing its clients with excellent legal services. As part of that commitment, we often need to collect personal information so that we can serve our clients. We obtain, use and disclose personal information responsibly and carefully and our privacy policy helps ensure our clients know how we handle their personal information.
What is Personal Information? Personal information is information about an individual person’s personal characteristics, such as name, age, ethnic origin, marital status, religion, education, contact information including home address, telephone, fax and e-mail, and health information. Why Do We Obtain Personal Information? As a law firm, we obtain, use, and disclose personal information in the course of providing legal services. We require personal information so that we can contact our clients, obtain information about their legal concerns, and develop and implement effective strategies to address those concerns. On occasion, we need to obtain personal information from third parties, such as health care providers or insurers, to endure that we have all necessary information. Paliare Roland recognizes that personal information is sensitive and only collects personal information as necessary. How Do We Collect Personal Information? For the most part, we obtain personal information either directly from our clients or with their consent. There are some limited instances where we obtain personal information without obtaining consent. For example, a number of Paliare Roland lawyers specialize in professional disciplinary proceedings, and may gather personal information in the course of an investigation into an allegation of professional misconduct. In such circumstances, we may not obtain the consent of the subject of the investigation because it could compromise the investigation.
Who Has Access to Personal Information?
Paliare Roland is a law firm in which a variety of people work may work together on a legal concern, including lawyers, articling students or law students, clerks, and administrative assistants, and have access to personal information. We take steps to ensure that personal information is used and disclosed appropriately, including:
ensuring lawyers and staff understand the importance of maintaining the security and confidentiality of personal information; developing and implementing policies for the collection, use, and protecting personal information against loss or theft; safeguarding personal information from unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification by restricting access to the office and files, using technological tools such as passwords to limit access to computer data, and ensuring that third parties who may have access to personal information in the course of services they provide to us follow proper privacy principles.
Can I Access My Personal Information From Paliare Roland? Yes. For the most part, you have a right to access your personal information and to know how it is or has been used. The Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, which governs the collection, use and disclosure of personal information, requires that we refuse to provide personal information in some circumstances, and allows us to protect privileged or confidential information if it falls into certain categories. For example, if personal information was collected in the course of investigating a legal concern for one of our clients, we have a legal duty to maintain the confidentiality of the information, unless our client consents to its release. As well, if personal information is incorrect, you have a right to correct or amend the information, or to have a statement of your disagreement appended to the file. How Do I Access Personal Information? Just ask us. If we need further information to ensure that we are fulfilling our obligations, we may ask that you provide us with a written request or further information. We will respond to any request promptly. There may be a modest cost to cover copying or other expenses, and if that is the case, we will advise you of the cost in advance. There may be some circumstances we are unable to provide the information because of our legal obligations, and if that is the case, we will provide an explanation for the refusal. Who Should I Contact at Paliare Roland? If you want to access personal information, or have questions about our personal information policy, please contact Karen Jones at tele: 416.646.4339; fax: 416.646.4301 or e-mail: karen.jones@paliareroland.com
Exceptional Advocates.
155 WELLINGTON ST WEST, 35th FLOOR TORONTO ON M5V 3H1 © 2017 Paliare Roland Rosenberg Rothstein | Privacy Policy | Disclaimer |  Law Firm Marketing | Cubicle Fugitive
